{
    "question": "This text is for questions 5-6    Sasha, sorry I can't come to your house to\r\nnight to do the Science project as we have\r\nplanned. My grandmother just came and she\r\nwants me to accompany her to my aunt's\r\nhouse. I will meet you at school tomorrow.\r\nErinda\r\n__________________________\r\n6. \"... she wants me to accompany her...\r\nThe underlined word refers to...\r\nA. Sasha's grandmother\r\nB. Erinda's grandmother\r\nC. My grandmother\r\nD. My aunt\r\nhis text is for questions 7-8\r\nANNOUNCEMENT\r\n\u200b",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>B. Erinda&#039;s grandmother</p>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "the-synonym-of-renowned-is-a-acceptable-b-well-known-c-signi-324",
            "question": "The synonym of \"renowned\" is     a. acceptable\r\nb. well-known\r\nc. significant\r\nd. accomplished\r\ne. modern\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>well-known = terkenal</p><p></p><p>Semoga terbantu, maap kalo salah. Kalo bener jan lupa jadiin jawaban tercerdas yak\u270c</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><h2>B. WELL - KNOWN = TERKENAL</h2>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-perbedaan-dan-persamaan-supermarket-dan-toko-grosir-570",
            "question": "Apa perbedaan dan persamaan supermarket dan toko grosir",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>toko grosir: harga nya lebih murah jualan nya </p><p>                    banyak juga macam macam </p><p>                     tapi klo di beli harus beli grosiran</p><p>                     tempat pedagang beli</p><p>supermarket:persedianya terjangkau beli nya          </p><p>                      juga deket dan banyak tempat </p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p>smoga membantu yahh</p><p></p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "jakarta-isthan-sidoarjo-179",
            "question": "Jakarta is....than sidoarjo",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>big</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>artinya lebih besar</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "jonia-driver-3-monts-ago-102",
            "question": "Joni....a driver 3 monts ago\r\n\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Joni <strong>w</strong><strong>a</strong><strong>s</strong><strong> </strong>a driver 3 month ago</p><p>(joni adalah seorang supir 3 bulan yg lalu)</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>kalimat nya adalah pola kalimat simple past tense yg menyatakan pristwa di masa lalu.</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "10-which-statement-is-not-true-based-in-on-the-text-a-dina-got-777",
            "question": "10. Which statement is NOT TRUE    based in on the text?\r\na. Dina got up very late\r\nb. Dina did not even have breakfast\r\nc. Dina is as old as her sister\r\nd. Dina took very quick bath\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>A. Dina got very late</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>SORRY BANGET KALAU SALAH</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "6-the-most-distinguishing-characteristic-of-an-elephant-is-364",
            "question": "6. The most distinguishing characteristic of an    elephant is.....\r\n(A). its clumsiness\r\n(B). its thick legs\r\n(C). its large body\r\n(D). its long nose \r\n\r\nartinya....\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>D. Its long nose</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Yang paling membedakan dari karakteristik gajah adalah D. hidungnya yang panjang :)</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "it-id-a-kind-of-wild-animal-it-likes-eating-meat-it-has-sharp-c-860",
            "question": "It id a kind of wild animal. It likes eating meat. It has Sharp claws and big hair\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>its a lion :o ..........</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>........</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "what-is-the-climax-of-the-strory-true-friends-once-upon-a-time-909",
            "question": "What is the climax of the strory?    True Friends\r\n\r\n Once upon a time, there were two close friends who were walking through the forest together. They knew that anything dangerous can happen any time in the forest. So they promised each other that they would always be together in any case of danger.\r\n\r\n Suddenly, they saw a large bear getting closer toward them. One of them climbed a nearby tree at once. But unfortunately the other one did not know how to climb up the tree. So being led by his common sense, he lay down on the ground breathless and pretended to be a dead man.\r\n\r\n The bear came near the one who was lying on the ground. It smelt in his ears, and slowly left the place because the bears do not want to touch the dead creatures. After that, the friend on the tree came down and asked his friend that was on the ground, \"Friend, what did the bear whisper into your ears?\" The other friend replied, \"Just now the bear advised me not to believe a false friend.\"\r\n\r\n Moral of the Story- A true friend in need is a friend indeed",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Apa klimaks dari cerita tersebut?</p><p></p><p>Teman sejati</p><p></p><p>Alkisah, ada dua orang sahabat yang sedang berjalan bersama di hutan. Mereka tahu bahwa segala sesuatu yang berbahaya dapat terjadi kapan saja di hutan. Jadi mereka berjanji satu sama lain bahwa mereka akan selalu bersama dalam keadaan bahaya apa pun.</p><p></p><p>Tiba-tiba, mereka melihat seekor beruang besar mendekat ke arah mereka. Salah satu dari mereka memanjat pohon terdekat sekaligus. Namun sayangnya yang satunya tidak tahu bagaimana cara memanjat pohon tersebut. Jadi dibimbing oleh akal sehatnya, dia berbaring di tanah dengan terengah-engah dan berpura-pura menjadi orang mati.</p><p></p><p>Beruang itu mendekati orang yang terbaring di tanah. Itu tercium di telinganya, dan perlahan meninggalkan tempat itu karena beruang tidak mau menyentuh makhluk mati. Setelah itu, teman di pohon itu turun dan bertanya kepada temannya yang ada di tanah, \"Teman, apa yang dibisikkan beruang ke telingamu?\" Teman yang lain menjawab, \"Baru saja beruang itu menasihati saya untuk tidak mempercayai teman palsu.\"</p><p></p><p>Moral of the Story- Teman sejati yang membutuhkan adalah teman sejati.</p><p></p><p>Semoga membantu^^</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "the-month-is-april-an-june-isi-titik2-n-351",
            "question": "The............ month is............. april an june. isi titik2 nya\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>the May month is between april and june</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "what-ia-the-main-idea-of-the-paragraph-674",
            "question": "What ia the main idea of the paragraph\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p></p><p><strong>I want to help you, but where is the paragraph??</strong></p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}